{ "results": [
	{
        "answer1": "appropriate",
        "answer2": "appropriateness",
        "answer3": "appropriately",
        "answer4": "most appropriate",
        "answerCorrect": "appropriate",
        "createdAt": "2016-01-11T12:28:12.027Z",
        "nameTest": "test01",
        "objectId": "1XDot5x7vo",
        "question": "The manager said that it is _____ to test emergency equipment frequently to avoid any malfunction.",
        "updatedAt": "2016-01-11T12:28:12.027Z"
    },
	{
        "answer1": "destinations",
        "answer2": "treatments",
        "answer3": "goals",
        "answer4": "opinions",
        "answerCorrect": "goals",
        "createdAt": "2016-01-11T09:24:39.143Z",
        "nameTest": "test01",
        "objectId": "230To1r56d",
        "question": "The _____ of the internship program are to help job seekers strengthen their professional skills and make them suitable for careers they are looking for.",
        "updatedAt": "2016-01-11T09:26:34.117Z"
    },
	{
        "answer1": "leave",
        "answer2": "leaving",
        "answer3": "to leave",
        "answer4": "have left",
        "answerCorrect": "leave",
        "createdAt": "2016-01-11T09:06:52.560Z",
        "nameTest": "test01",
        "objectId": "28OQ5znUoS",
        "question": "Even though assigned tasks are somewhat complex, we will have to complete them before we _____ for the day.",
        "updatedAt": "2016-01-11T09:08:26.396Z"
    },
	{
        "answer1": "develops",
        "answer2": "developing",
        "answer3": "development",
        "answer4": "developed",
        "answerCorrect": "development",
        "createdAt": "2016-01-11T07:07:59.378Z",
        "nameTest": "test01",
        "objectId": "2EevmWTAY7",
        "question": "The effects of affordable housing _____ in rural areas will be discussed at the conference.",
        "updatedAt": "2016-01-11T07:09:47.851Z"
    },
	{
        "answer1": "Due to",
        "answer2": "While",
        "answer3": "In that",
        "answer4": "In case",
        "answerCorrect": "Due to",
        "createdAt": "2016-01-11T12:37:24.437Z",
        "nameTest": "test01",
        "objectId": "36fQrFSjBZ",
        "question": "_____ her hard work and commitment to the company, Ms. Ramirez was promoted to the head of the public relations department.",
        "updatedAt": "2016-01-11T12:37:24.437Z"
    },
	{
        "answer1": "they",
        "answer2": "them",
        "answer3": "their",
        "answer4": "those",
        "answerCorrect": "their",
        "createdAt": "2016-01-11T09:15:35.945Z",
        "nameTest": "test01",
        "objectId": "4nvi5RzgMG",
        "question": "The two divisions have unveiled _____ plan to set aside millions of dollars to invest in a very lucrative field.",
        "updatedAt": "2016-01-11T09:17:10.290Z"
    },
	{
        "answer1": "If",
        "answer2": "Should",
        "answer3": "Whether",
        "answer4": "As though",
        "answerCorrect": "Should",
        "createdAt": "2016-01-11T09:22:50.496Z",
        "nameTest": "test01",
        "objectId": "4vVzhOsX58",
        "question": "_____ anyone wish to access the information on the status of his or her order, the password should be entered.",
        "updatedAt": "2016-01-11T09:24:21.189Z"
    },
	{
        "answer1": "propose",
        "answer2": "proposed",
        "answer3": "proposes",
        "answer4": "to proposing",
        "answerCorrect": "proposed",
        "createdAt": "2016-01-11T12:43:27.245Z",
        "nameTest": "test01",
        "objectId": "5COjcJS1S9",
        "question": "The enclosed documents summarize _____ changes to the existing overtime regulations.",
        "updatedAt": "2016-01-11T12:43:27.245Z"
    },
	{
        "answer1": "impression",
        "answer2": "impress",
        "answer3": "impresses",
        "answer4": "impressed",
        "answerCorrect": "impressed",
        "createdAt": "2016-01-11T10:15:12.124Z",
        "nameTest": "test01",
        "objectId": "6kD2YXqVao",
        "question": "The more we spent with the sales team, the more _____ we were with their innovative marketing skills.",
        "updatedAt": "2016-01-11T10:15:12.124Z"
    },
	{
        "answer1": "nearly",
        "answer2": "off",
        "answer3": "close",
        "answer4": "about",
        "answerCorrect": "about",
        "createdAt": "2016-01-11T12:34:01.989Z",
        "nameTest": "test01",
        "objectId": "8DgjHYJLGR",
        "question": "Ms. Walters was _____ to make a presentation on how to increase revenue when I entered the room.",
        "updatedAt": "2016-01-11T12:34:01.989Z"
    },
	{
        "answer1": "compare",
        "answer2": "compared",
        "answer3": "comparable",
        "answer4": "comparing",
        "answerCorrect": "comparable",
        "createdAt": "2016-01-11T12:46:31.887Z",
        "nameTest": "test01",
        "objectId": "8PZ9ZUncAh",
        "question": "Applicants must possess a master of business administration or _____ experience in a related field.",
        "updatedAt": "2016-01-11T12:46:31.887Z"
    },
	{
        "answer1": "Whether",
        "answer2": "Since",
        "answer3": "For",
        "answer4": "Which",
        "answerCorrect": "Since",
        "createdAt": "2016-01-11T10:24:19.345Z",
        "nameTest": "test01",
        "objectId": "Am3fLmmcph",
        "question": "_____ none of the participants has showed any interest, numerous outdoor activities have to be cancelled.",
        "updatedAt": "2016-01-11T10:24:19.345Z"
    },
	{
        "answer1": "their",
        "answer2": "they",
        "answer3": "themselves",
        "answer4": "theirs",
        "answerCorrect": "their",
        "createdAt": "2016-01-10T10:49:26.823Z",
        "nameTest": "test01",
        "objectId": "DsjDEnJZSB",
        "question": "Those who have questions concerning fringe benefits are advised to consult _____ employee handbook.",
        "updatedAt": "2016-01-11T04:04:04.804Z"
    },
	{
        "answer1": "practice",
        "answer2": "rewind",
        "answer3": "record",
        "answer4": "attend",
        "answerCorrect": "record",
        "createdAt": "2016-01-11T09:08:39.647Z",
        "nameTest": "test01",
        "objectId": "GXBjdhjeDg",
        "question": "All workers are required to use the sheet provided to _____ their working hours and have their manager sign the form to verify the hours at the end of each day.",
        "updatedAt": "2016-01-11T09:10:49.748Z"
    },
	{
        "answer1": "who",
        "answer2": "when",
        "answer3": "what",
        "answer4": "whom",
        "answerCorrect": "who",
        "createdAt": "2016-01-11T12:18:31.669Z",
        "nameTest": "test01",
        "objectId": "IQv5XdkesN",
        "question": "Customers _____ wish to return merchandise within 7 days of purchase must present the valid receipt to the store.",
        "updatedAt": "2016-01-11T12:24:32.434Z"
    },
	{
        "answer1": "precaution",
        "answer2": "advice",
        "answer3": "rule",
        "answer4": "idea",
        "answerCorrect": "precaution",
        "createdAt": "2016-01-11T12:20:23.011Z",
        "nameTest": "test01",
        "objectId": "IUYazDuq2c",
        "question": "All laboratory employees make it a point to take every _____ to avoid potential hazards.",
        "updatedAt": "2016-01-11T12:24:40.601Z"
    },
	{
        "answer1": "In spite of",
        "answer2": "Prior to",
        "answer3": "However",
        "answer4": "Yet",
        "answerCorrect": "In spite of",
        "createdAt": "2016-01-11T12:44:46.917Z",
        "nameTest": "test01",
        "objectId": "JEEGnPLLS7",
        "question": "_____ regular inspections, accidental system problems arise from time to time.",
        "updatedAt": "2016-01-11T12:44:46.917Z"
    },
	{
        "answer1": "detain",
        "answer2": "associate",
        "answer3": "conduct",
        "answer4": "foresee",
        "answerCorrect": "conduct",
        "createdAt": "2016-01-11T12:32:20.777Z",
        "nameTest": "test01",
        "objectId": "JavAYDr7nE",
        "question": "It is necessary to _____ a thorough survey in order for us to obtain highly desirable sites for our new headquarters.",
        "updatedAt": "2016-01-11T12:32:20.777Z"
    },
	{
        "answer1": "accommodation",
        "answer2": "policy",
        "answer3": "handling",
        "answer4": "measure",
        "answerCorrect": "policy",
        "createdAt": "2016-01-11T12:54:20.344Z",
        "nameTest": "test01",
        "objectId": "Nt2jERIWHh",
        "question": "The library has announced a new _____ that all borrowed books must be returned 5 business days from the checkout date.",
        "updatedAt": "2016-01-11T12:54:20.344Z"
    },
	{
        "answer1": "whole",
        "answer2": "inclusive",
        "answer3": "exceptional",
        "answer4": "multiple",
        "answerCorrect": "exceptional",
        "createdAt": "2016-01-10T10:47:32.470Z",
        "nameTest": "test01",
        "objectId": "OOPSq4FaLp",
        "question": "The employee-of-the-year prizes will be awarded to employees who demonstrated _____ contribution to the company's overall sales.",
        "updatedAt": "2016-01-11T04:03:54.248Z"
    },
	{
        "answer1": "Invite",
        "answer2": "Invitations",
        "answer3": "Inviting",
        "answer4": "Invitation",
        "answerCorrect": "Invitations",
        "createdAt": "2016-01-10T10:43:59.691Z",
        "nameTest": "test01",
        "objectId": "Olw0XwmWIT",
        "question": "_____ for the money management seminar will be forwarded to all the managers tomorrow.",
        "updatedAt": "2016-01-11T04:03:42.558Z"
    },
	{
        "answer1": "into",
        "answer2": "throughout",
        "answer3": "on",
        "answer4": "as",
        "answerCorrect": "throughout",
        "createdAt": "2016-01-11T12:51:04.176Z",
        "nameTest": "test01",
        "objectId": "Rh3WBNkXvU",
        "question": "Information on events occurring in the theater _____ the year is available through our website.",
        "updatedAt": "2016-01-11T12:51:04.176Z"
    },
	{
        "answer1": "see",
        "answer2": "seen",
        "answer3": "seeing",
        "answer4": "has been",
        "answerCorrect": "has been",
        "createdAt": "2016-01-11T07:04:15.744Z",
        "nameTest": "test01",
        "objectId": "S1xZIwb0qg",
        "question": "The fitness club _____ a steadily increasing number of customers and is eager to develop new programs.",
        "updatedAt": "2016-01-11T09:01:38.734Z"
    },
	{
        "answer1": "description",
        "answer2": "attention",
        "answer3": "information",
        "answer4": "mistake",
        "answerCorrect": "description",
        "createdAt": "2016-01-10T10:50:42.485Z",
        "nameTest": "test01",
        "objectId": "T1qi7eaPCY",
        "question": "The summary contains not only a technical _____ but also solutions to adverse effects of urban renewal developments.",
        "updatedAt": "2016-01-11T04:04:39.719Z"
    },
	{
        "answer1": "the other",
        "answer2": "another",
        "answer3": "other",
        "answer4": "one another",
        "answerCorrect": "one another",
        "createdAt": "2016-01-11T12:52:45.024Z",
        "nameTest": "test01",
        "objectId": "V8eLLDXWPw",
        "question": "Through the Internet people are discovering new ways to share relevant information with _____.",
        "updatedAt": "2016-01-11T12:52:45.024Z"
    },
	{
        "answer1": "abbreviated",
        "answer2": "terminated",
        "answer3": "scheduled",
        "answer4": "postponed",
        "answerCorrect": "postponed",
        "createdAt": "2016-01-11T12:48:18.881Z",
        "nameTest": "test01",
        "objectId": "WWtZ9aLvob",
        "question": "The recruitment advertising meeting that was scheduled for tomorrow has been _____ until next week.",
        "updatedAt": "2016-01-11T12:48:18.881Z"
    },
	{
        "answer1": "variety",
        "answer2": "variably",
        "answer3": "variation",
        "answer4": "various",
        "answerCorrect": "various",
        "createdAt": "2016-01-10T10:52:22.033Z",
        "nameTest": "test01",
        "objectId": "XSPUZeFk2r",
        "question": "The conference's keynote speaker addressed _____ impacts of digital technology on the current music industry.",
        "updatedAt": "2016-01-11T04:04:31.550Z"
    },
	{
        "answer1": "relatively",
        "answer2": "slightly",
        "answer3": "usually",
        "answer4": "vaguely",
        "answerCorrect": "usually",
        "createdAt": "2016-01-11T06:55:51.960Z",
        "nameTest": "test01",
        "objectId": "aElAblkAip",
        "question": "Documents with a secret nature are _____ retained in each director's safety deposit box.",
        "updatedAt": "2016-01-11T07:03:39.200Z"
    },
	{
        "answer1": "involved",
        "answer2": "agreed",
        "answer3": "announced",
        "answer4": "maintained",
        "answerCorrect": "announced",
        "createdAt": "2016-01-11T09:21:10.410Z",
        "nameTest": "test01",
        "objectId": "f8kXXw58vq",
        "question": "The purchasing department _____ the drastic changes to the purchasing practice with outside suppliers.",
        "updatedAt": "2016-01-11T09:22:36.428Z"
    },
	{
        "answer1": "rise",
        "answer2": "arisen",
        "answer3": "rose",
        "answer4": "rising",
        "answerCorrect": "rising",
        "createdAt": "2016-01-11T12:40:08.311Z",
        "nameTest": "test01",
        "objectId": "fi51dPjVM3",
        "question": "Due to _____ fuel prices, the company has decided to add a surcharge to all deliveries.",
        "updatedAt": "2016-01-11T12:40:08.311Z"
    },
	{
        "answer1": "regularly",
        "answer2": "quickly",
        "answer3": "softly",
        "answer4": "tiredly",
        "answerCorrect": "quickly",
        "createdAt": "2016-01-11T12:41:41.035Z",
        "nameTest": "test01",
        "objectId": "htWcTmN8so",
        "question": "As the company's strongest competitor released a new line of fall clothing, NTR Inc. moved _____ to introduce its new leather jackets.",
        "updatedAt": "2016-01-11T12:41:41.035Z"
    },
	{
        "answer1": "overall",
        "answer2": "successfull",
        "answer3": "wealthy",
        "answer4": "delighted",
        "answerCorrect": "successfull",
        "createdAt": "2016-01-11T07:05:51.852Z",
        "nameTest": "test01",
        "objectId": "iBn2Qn51MY",
        "question": "The job fair held in the City Center last week is considered the most _____ one so far, with over 3000 people in attendance.",
        "updatedAt": "2016-01-11T07:07:43.931Z"
    },
	{
        "answer1": "following",
        "answer2": "more than",
        "answer3": "because",
        "answer4": "unless",
        "answerCorrect": "because",
        "createdAt": "2016-01-11T09:13:40.931Z",
        "nameTest": "test01",
        "objectId": "ida2K4wpKV",
        "question": "The team members have the same opinions on the matter _____ they shared the same information.",
        "updatedAt": "2016-01-11T09:15:05.644Z"
    },
	{
        "answer1": "Otherwise",
        "answer2": "Despite",
        "answer3": "Regarding",
        "answer4": "Although",
        "answerCorrect": "Although",
        "createdAt": "2016-01-11T09:17:24.009Z",
        "nameTest": "test01",
        "objectId": "mzIqTE2EFg",
        "question": "_____ proficiency in German would be of much help, it is not a requirement for the advertised position.",
        "updatedAt": "2016-01-11T09:18:55.142Z"
    },
	{
        "answer1": "probabilities",
        "answer2": "probability",
        "answer3": "probable",
        "answer4": "probably",
        "answerCorrect": "probably",
        "createdAt": "2016-01-11T12:49:39.263Z",
        "nameTest": "test01",
        "objectId": "nBKJJFtECw",
        "question": "The expansion of the natural history museum is most _____ the cause of significant revenue increases.",
        "updatedAt": "2016-01-11T12:49:39.263Z"
    },
	{
        "answer1": "on",
        "answer2": "between",
        "answer3": "by",
        "answer4": "except",
        "answerCorrect": "by",
        "createdAt": "2016-01-11T07:10:00.680Z",
        "nameTest": "test01",
        "objectId": "nf4E1elQaC",
        "question": "Because the annual budget report must be submitted _____ the end of the month, employees are busy calculating figures.",
        "updatedAt": "2016-01-11T07:11:14.661Z"
    },
	{
        "answer1": "origin",
        "answer2": "original",
        "answer3": "originally",
        "answer4": "originated",
        "answerCorrect": "originally",
        "createdAt": "2016-01-11T12:38:59.272Z",
        "nameTest": "test01",
        "objectId": "rlu83LQMCT",
        "question": "The unexpected operating complexity was more serious than _____ anticipated.",
        "updatedAt": "2016-01-11T12:38:59.272Z"
    },
	{
        "answer1": "resisting",
        "answer2": "resistant",
        "answer3": "resisted",
        "answer4": "resistance",
        "answerCorrect": "resistance",
        "createdAt": "2016-01-11T09:11:24.149Z",
        "nameTest": "test01",
        "objectId": "sTbEAAkN3S",
        "question": "Even if residents in the area have shown strong _____ to the project, the city government may not be hesitant to proceed with it.",
        "updatedAt": "2016-01-11T09:13:16.997Z"
    },
	{
        "answer1": "favorable",
        "answer2": "routine",
        "answer3": "sincere",
        "answer4": "recent",
        "answerCorrect": "routine",
        "createdAt": "2016-01-11T12:35:52.677Z",
        "nameTest": "test01",
        "objectId": "stLsvY2aAW",
        "question": "Mr. Lee takes care of several _____ tasks, such as sorting papers and filing documents in the cabinet.",
        "updatedAt": "2016-01-11T12:35:52.677Z"
    },
	{
        "answer1": "fortunate",
        "answer2": "fortunes",
        "answer3": "fortune",
        "answer4": "fortunately",
        "answerCorrect": "fortunately",
        "createdAt": "2016-01-11T09:19:25.997Z",
        "nameTest": "test01",
        "objectId": "waUYvRYfhy",
        "question": "We had to spend the whole month searching for better solutions, and _____ customers were impressed by our efforts.",
        "updatedAt": "2016-01-11T09:20:54.155Z"
    }
] }
